(Sheldon:)Some will be successful,
(Sheldon:)some may be homeless.
(Sheldon:)It's fun to think about.
I wonder which one's Halley.
(Amy:)Kind of hard to see the names.
(Penny:)Mm, that one kind of
looks like Bernadette.
(Amy:)They all look the same to me.
(Penny(off):)Guys,
(Raj:)she's my goddaughter,
(Raj:)I think I'll know
when I see her.
(Penny:)That one.
(Amy:)Well, that was quite a day.
(Stuart:)It was.
(Sheldon:)Bernadette had her baby,
(Sheldon:)I made it to Wizarding World,
(Sheldon:)and now it is time to complete
(Sheldon:)your birthday celebration.
Hankius
pankius.
(Amy:)I was afraid you'd be too tired.
(Sheldon:)Amy, I just saw a magic train
(Sheldon:)and reported somebody
for cutting the line.
(Sheldon:)If that's not foreplay,
I don't know what is.